Guide to the Gerald Stern Papers, 1920s-2012 SC.2007.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, 1950-2007; IV.
  - Significant Others, 1977-2006; 2.
    - Rock, Judy, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Robinson, Judith R., 1992-1996 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Sharrow, Sheba, 1988-2004 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Smith, Nancy, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Sussman, Harriet, 1977-1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Rae Marie, 1986-2004 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Abigail, 1988-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Trimble, Dranda, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Wayne, Jane, 1983-1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - White, Sarah, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Yerushalmi, Oprah, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Zak, Victoria (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Acquaintances, 1948-2007; 3.
    - A, 1981-2005 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - B, 1967-2007 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - C, 1973-2004 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - D, 1963-2007 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - E-G, 1963-2004 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - H-J, 1959-2006 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - K, 1950-2006 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - L, 1975-2006 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - M, 1948-2005 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - N-O, 1975-2002 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - P-Q, 1974-2005 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - R, 1974-2005 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Sa-Sl, 1975-2006 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Sm-Sz, 1981-2005 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - T-V, 1975-2005 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - W-Z, 1971-2004 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 2015 Addition, 2007-2011
      - Bernat, Edwina, 2007-2011 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Ceniza, Sherry, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Coe, Bruce, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Drew, Naomi, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Holt, Rush, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - Mazur, Gail, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - McVey, Scott & Hela, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Musher, Noah, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Sigstedt, Val, 2008-2012 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Weingart, Reva, 2006-2009 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Robert Summers, 1955-1971; 4.
    - Letters to Stern, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Letter from Summers to his wife (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Eulogies on Summers (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Typescript of The Demented (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Typescript of Florence Hobbes, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Typescript of The Paris Exercise, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Typescript of chapters 1-10 of The Swindle (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Politicians, 1980-2006; 5.
    - Rush Holt, 2002-2006 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ed Koch, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Dick Thornburgh, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Requests and Reviews, 1966-2006; 6.
    This subseries contains requests for Stern's poems for journals and for publication in anthologies, reviews of other poets' works, and requests for participation in various projects and events.
    - Readings, Events, Projects, etc. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Reviews, Poems, Essays, etc (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Introductions (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Anthologies, 1979-1994 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Anthologies, 1995-2007 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Journals, A, 1966-2005 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Journals, B-F, 1977-2006 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Journals, G-L, 1962-2005 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Journals, M-O, 1969-2005 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Journals, Pa-Pn, 1975-2004 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Journals, Po-Q, 1975-2005 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Journals, R-T, 1970-2003 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Journals, U-Z, 1982-2005 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - 2015 Addition, 1997-2012
      - Audio Visual Projects, 2007-2009 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Anthologies etc., 2003-2012 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Magazines/Poems & Prose, 1997-2012 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - Requests for Previews and Introductions, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Well-Known Poets, 1948-2007; 7.
    - Ackerman, Diane, 1985-2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Addonisio, Kim, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Asekoff, Louis, 1989-2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Banks, Russell, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Baraka, Amiri, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Barnstone, Aliki, 1995-2005 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Barnstone, Willis, 1994-2007 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Bell, Marvin, 1977-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Black, Sophie Cabot (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Bly, Robert, 1968-1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Boruch, Marianne, 1988-1990 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Busch, Frederick (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Carruth, Hayden, 1987-2004 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Clover, Joshua, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Codrescu, Andrei, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Coleman, Wanda, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Collier, Michael, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Collins, Billy, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Connellan, Leo, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Cooper, Jane, 1976-2002 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Derricotte, Toi, 1989-2005 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Dickey, James, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Digges, Deborah, 1984-1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Doty, Mary, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Dove, Rita, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Dungy, Camille, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Dunn, Stephen, 1981-2004 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Emanuel, Lynn, 1987-1999 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Espoda, Martin (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Gallagher, Tess, 1979-1983 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Gander, Forrest, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Garrison, Deborah, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Gay, Ross (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Gilbert, Jack, 1948-2005 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Ginsburg, Allen, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Gluck, Louise, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Goldbarth, Albert (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Graham, Jorie (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Gregg, Linda, 1977-1999 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Grossman, Allen, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Haba, Jim, 1987-2003 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Hacker, Marilyn, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Hall, Donald, 1974-2001 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Halpern, Daniel, 1982-2006 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Hamill, Sam, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Harper, Michael, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Hazley, Richard - letters to, 1949-1978 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Hazley, Richard - letters from, 1950-1997 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Herrera, Juan Felipe, 1990-2004 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Heyen, Bill, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Hicok, Bob, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Hirsch, Edward, 1976-1998 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Hirshfield, Jane, 2004-2006 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Hoagland, Tony, 1989-2006 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Honga, Garrett, 1983-1994 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Howard, Richard, 1975-2004 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Ignatow, David, 1977-1991 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Justice, Donald, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Kasdorf, Julia, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Katrovas, Richard, 1983-2007 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Kaufman, Shirley, 1987-2004 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Kessler, Milton, 1977-1991 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Kinnell, Galway, 1977-2006 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Kizer, Carolyn, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Koestenbaum, Phyllis, 1977-1997 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Knight, Etheridge, 1977-1987 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Kulick, Bill and Kunitz, Stanley, 1968-2004 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Lauterbach, Ann, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Larkin, Joan, 2004-2007 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Laux, Dorianne, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Lee, Li-Young, 1982-1999 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Levertov, Denise, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Levine, Philip, 1977-1998 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Levine, Philip, 1982-1994 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Levine, Philip, 1990-1994 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Levine, Philip, 1988-2005 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Levis, Larry, 1990-1996 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Lindeman, Jack, 1977-2004 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Louis, Adrian C., 2006 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Lux, Thomas, 1988-2007 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Macari, Anne Marie, 1998-2005 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - MacDonald, Cynthia, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Marshall, Jack, 1982-1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Martinez, Dionesio D., 1990-1998 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Matthews, Bill, 1998-2005 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - McCartney, Paul (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - McHugh, Heather, 1977-2006 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Mead, Jane, 1991-2005 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Meredith, William (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Merwin, William, 1978-2005 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Mills, Ralph, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Mitchell, Susan, 1964-1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Moore, Honor, 1988-2001 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Mullen, Laura, 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Muske, Carol, 1992-2003 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Myers, Jack, 1984-1994 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Nurske, Dennis, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Nye, Naomi Shihab, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - O'Driscoll, Dennis, 2005 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Olds, Sharon, 1984-1990 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Oliver, Mary, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Orlovitz, Gil, 1967-1988 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Orr, Greg, 1984-1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Ostriker, Alicia, 1975-2006 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Parini, Joy, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Pastan, Linda, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Phillips, Carl, 2006 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Pierce, Kathleen, 1989-2006 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Piercy, Marge, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Pinsker, Sanford, 1974-1992 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 1985-2005 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Pletzinger, Thomas, 2002-2005 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Plumly, Stanley, 1977-2005 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Prose, Francine, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Purpura, Lia, 1989-2007 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Ramke, Bin, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Ray, David, 1981-2002 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - Rector, Liam, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Redel, Victoria, 1994-2000 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Reiss, James, 1977-1992 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - Revell, Donald, 1988-2006 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Rivard, David, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Roberts, Leonard R., 1982-2007 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Rumkorf, Peter, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - Ryan, Michael, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Sadoff, Ira, 1994-2004 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Salamun, Tomaz, 1998-2006 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Schulman, Grace, 1976-2006 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Schwartz, Lynne Sharon, 1983-2007 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Seshadri, Vijay, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Simic, Charles, 1990-2005 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Simpson, Louis, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Smith, Bruce, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Charlie (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Soto, Gary, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Spark, Muriel, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Strand, Mark (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - St. John, David (Box 19, Folder 61)
    - Summers, Robert, 1968-1977 (Box 19, Folder 62)
    - Svoboda, Terese, 1990-1995 (Box 19, Folder 63)
    - Troupe, Quincy, 2003 (Box 19, Folder 64)
    - Twitcell, Chase, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 65)
    - Valentine, Jean, 1976-2005 (Box 19, Folder 66)
    - Voigt, Ellen, 1992-2007 (Box 19, Folder 67)
    - Vogelsang, Arthur, 1978-2005 (Box 19, Folder 68)
    - Wakoski, Diane, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 69)
    - Waters, Michael, 2003-2006 (Box 19, Folder 70)
    - Weaver, Afaa Michael, 1992-2007 (Box 19, Folder 71)
    - Weigl, Bruce, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 72)
    - Willard, Nancy (Box 19, Folder 73)
    - Willeford, Charles, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 74)
    - Williams, Charles K., 1983-2004 (Box 19, Folder 75)
    - Wilner, Eleanor, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 76)
    - Wright, Annie, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 77)
    - Wright, Charles, 1977-1992 (Box 19, Folder 78)
    - Wright, James, 1977-2005 (Box 19, Folder 79)
    - Young Bear, Ray, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 80)
    - Zagjewski, Adam, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 81)
    - Zimmer, Paul, 1976-1992 (Box 19, Folder 82)
    - 2015 Addition, 1995-2012
      - Asekoff, L.S., 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 18)
      - Barbarese, Joe, 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 19)
      - Barnstone, Willis, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - Bauer, Curtis, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 21)
      - Beatty, Jan, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 22)
      - Beisch, June (Box 50, Folder 23)
      - Bell, Marvin, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 24)
      - Boutelle, Anne, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 25)
      - Briccetti, Lee, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 26)
      - Buckley, Christopher, 2008-2012 (Box 50, Folder 27)
      - Budy, Andrea Hollander, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 28)
      - Burkard, Michael, 2007-2009 (Box 50, Folder 29)
      - Cole, Peter, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 30)
      - Collier, Michael, 2009-2012 (Box 50, Folder 31)
      - Collins, Billy, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 32)
      - del Vecchio, Gloria, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 33)
      - de Niord, Chard, 2006-2012 (Box 50, Folder 34)
      - Dernier, Ann, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 35)
      - Derricote, Toi, 2009-2012 (Box 50, Folder 36)
      - Desht, Martin, 2008-2012 (Box 50, Folder 37)
      - Dickman, Matthew, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 38)
      - Doty, Mark, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 39)
      - Dove, Rita, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 40)
      - Dunn, Stephen, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 41)
      - Espada, Martin, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 42)
      - Friedman, Jeff, 2010-2012 (Box 50, Folder 43)
      - Garrison, Deborah, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 44)
      - Gaspar, Frank, 2006-2012 (Box 50, Folder 45)
      - Gay, Ross, 2009-2012 (Box 50, Folder 46)
      - Gilbert, Jack, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 47)
      - Goldbarth, Albert (Box 50, Folder 48)
      - Goodrich, Christopher, 2007-2010 (Box 50, Folder 49)
      - Graham, Jorie (Box 50, Folder 50)
      - Gregg, Linda, 2009-2011 (Box 50, Folder 51)
      - Gubernat, Susan, 2007-2008 (Box 50, Folder 52)
      - Haba, Jim and Erica, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 53)
      - Hacker, Marilyn, 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 54)
      - Hahn, Kimiko (Box 50, Folder 55)
      - Hall, Judith, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 56)
      - Hamilton, David, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 57)
      - Heyan, Bill, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 58)
      - Hirsch, Edward, 2008-2011 (Box 50, Folder 59)
      - Hirschfield, June, 2007-2011 (Box 50, Folder 60)
      - Hoagland, Tony, 2007-2009 (Box 50, Folder 61)
      - Howell, Rebecca, 2008-2011 (Box 50, Folder 62)
      - Jackson, Rick, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 63)
      - Kaminsky, Ilya, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 64)
      - Katrovas, Richard, 2007-2010 (Box 50, Folder 65)
      - Keys, Kerry, 2007-2011 (Box 50, Folder 66)
      - Kirby, David, 2008-2010 (Box 50, Folder 67)
      - Kinnell, Galway and Bobby Bristol, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 68)
      - Longstroth, Gail, 2012 (Box 50, Folder 69)
      - Larkin, Joan, 2009-2011 (Box 50, Folder 70)
      - Laux, Dorianne, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 71)
      - Lee, Li-Young, 2007-2009 (Box 50, Folder 72)
      - Lehman, David, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 73)
      - Lempert, Norbert (Box 50, Folder 74)
      - Levi, Jan Heller, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 75)
      - Levin, Lynn, 2007-2009 (Box 50, Folder 76)
      - Levin, Phillis, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 77)
      - Levine, Philip, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 78)
      - Levis, Larry (Box 50, Folder 79)
      - Lipton, Rob, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 80)
      - Logghe, Joan (Box 50, Folder 81)
      - Longenbach, James, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 82)
      - Longley, Michael, 2000 (Box 50, Folder 83)
      - Lux, Thomas, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 84)
      - Lynch, Alessandra, 2005-2008 (Box 50, Folder 85)
      - Lyman, Henry, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 86)
      - Macari, Anne Marie, 2002-2012 (Box 50, Folder 87)
      - Marcus, Morton, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 88)
      - Marshall, Jack, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 89)
      - Matthews, Sebastian, 2006-2009 (Box 50, Folder 90)
      - McCullough, Laura, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 91)
      - McDougal, Jo, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 92)
      - McGrath, Campbell, 2009-2011 (Box 50, Folder 93)
      - McHugh, Heather, 2007-2011 (Box 50, Folder 94)
      - McKee, Louis (Box 50, Folder 95)
      - Mead, Jane, 2008-2012 (Box 50, Folder 96)
      - Milar, Joe (Box 50, Folder 97)
      - Mitchell, Susan, 2009 (Box 50, Folder 98)
      - Morling, Malena, 2007-2009 (Box 50, Folder 99)
      - Moscaliuc, Mihaela, 2009-2012 (Box 50, Folder 100)
      - Moss, Stanley, 2010-2012 (Box 50, Folder 101)
      - Muldoon, Paul, 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 102)
      - Murray, Joan (Box 50, Folder 103)
      - Nathanson, Roy, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 104)
      - Ochester, Ed (Box 50, Folder 105)
      - O'Donnell, Mutt, 2008-2009 (Box 50, Folder 106)
      - Olds, Shavon, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 107)
      - Oresick, Peter, 1991-2012 (Box 50, Folder 108)
      - Ostriker, Alicia, 2009-2012 (Box 50, Folder 109)
      - Pasternack, Gary, 2008-2011 (Box 50, Folder 110)
      - Peirce, Kathleen, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 111)
      - Pinsky, Robert, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 112)
      - Pletzinger, Thomas, 2004-2013 (Box 50, Folder 113)
      - Plumly, Stanley, 2007 (Box 50, Folder 114)
      - Posner, Martha, 2007-2011 (Box 50, Folder 115)
      - Purpura, Lia, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 116)
      - Redel, Victoria, 2008-2012 (Box 50, Folder 117)
      - Reese, Henry, 2008 (Box 50, Folder 118)
      - Revell, David, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 119)
      - Richards, Peter, 2008-2011 (Box 50, Folder 120)
      - Rigsbee, David, 2009-2010 (Box 50, Folder 121)
      - Robbins, Doren, 2007-2012 (Box 50, Folder 122)
      - Rohrer, Matthew, 2011-2012 (Box 50, Folder 123)
      - Roffman, Rosaly, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 124)
      - Rosal, Patrick, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 125)
      - Sadoff, Ira, 2005-2012 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Schultz, Philip, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Schwartz, Howard, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Setton, Ruth, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Sexton, Megan, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Shulman, Grace, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Simon, Maurya, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Smith, Bruce, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Soldofsky, Alan, 2007-2010 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Stewart, Jack, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Stone, Bianca, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Stone, Ruth, 2009-2010 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Stricker, Meredith, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - Svobada, Terese, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - Swenson, Karen, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - Tiger, Madeline (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Timpane, John, 2012 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Turner, Brian, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Valentine, Jean, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 19)
      - Vogelsang, Arthur, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 20)
      - Voight, Ellen Bryant, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 21)
      - Vollmer, Judith, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 22)
      - Waldman, Anne, 2008 (Box 51, Folder 23)
      - Waldor, Peter, 1995-2012 (Box 51, Folder 24)
      - Wallace, Naomi, 2008-2010 (Box 51, Folder 25)
      - Ward, Christina, 2009-2010 (Box 51, Folder 26)
      - Waters, Michael, 2008-2012 (Box 51, Folder 27)
      - Watson, Ellen Dore, 2009-2011 (Box 51, Folder 28)
      - Weaver, Afaa, 2007-2012 (Box 51, Folder 29)
      - Wheeler, Susan, 2009 (Box 51, Folder 30)
      - Williams, C.K., 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 31)
      - Wilson, Jim, 2010-2012 (Box 51, Folder 32)
      - Zackheim, Michele, 2009-2011 (Box 51, Folder 33)
      - Zisquist, Linda, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Lesser-Known Poets, 1954-2007; 8.
    - General, 1980-2007 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Aggos, Julie (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, Maggie, 1980-1999 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Anghelaki-Rooke, Katerina, 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Balaban, John, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Balakian, Peter, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Balitas, Vincent D., 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Ball, Angela, 1988-1992 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Barbarese, John (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Barber, Al (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Barnstone, Tony, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Barr, Tina, 1983-2006 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Bass, Ellen, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Beckman, Joshua, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Behn, Robin, 1984-1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Bertolino, James, 1984-2005 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Bethel, Gar (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Biggs, Mary, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Black, Ralph, 1994-2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Blatt, Richard, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Bluestone, Steve and Blumenthal, Michael, 1992-2006 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Bosselaar, Laure-Anne and Boroson, Rebecca, 1991-2006 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Boutelle, Annie, 2004-2006 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Bowers, Neal, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Braun, Henry, 1975-1997 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Brass, Deborah, 1989-1995 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Bricetti, Lee, 2005-2007 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Bringhurst, Robert, 1987-1994 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Brothers, Connie, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Buckley, Christopher, 1990-2007 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Budy, Andrea Hollander, 1992-2000 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Burke, Judith, 1983-1993 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Burke, Shelley, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Burroway, Janet, 1990-2005 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Burrows, Anudas, 1990-1993 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Burrows, David (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Bursk, Chris (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Butler, Denis B., 1954-1955 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Calloway, Kathy, 1982-1989 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Capps, Ashley, 2006 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Carey, Michael, 1977-2002 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Castro, Jan, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Catellani, Catherine, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Cherry, Kelly, 1987-1989 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Chess, Rick, 1981-1988 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Chetwynd, Richard, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Cioffi, Vince, 1998-2000 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Cleary, Suzanne, 1983-2002 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Clewell, David, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Cole, Henri, 1982-1988 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Cole, Peter, 1980-2003 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Comparone, Elaine, 1978-1983 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Conoley, Gillian, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Corkery, Christopher, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Costanza, Gerald, 1974-2002 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Czury, Craig, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Dana, Robert, 1986-1999 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Daniels, Guy, 1968-1985 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Daniels, Jim, 1985-1997 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Daniels, Kate, 1982-2003 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Davis, Chris, 1987-1995 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Del Vecchio, Gloria C., 1975-2003 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Deming, Alison Hawthorne, 1993-2001 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Desht, Martin J., 1992-2007 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - DeNiord, Chard, 1987-2006 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Di Suvero, Victor, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Dobkin, Alix, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Dodd, Wayne, 1988-1996 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Dolin, Sharon, 1995-2003 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Doubiago, Sharon, 1985-2004 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Dow, Philip, 1975-1993 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - Duemer, Joseph, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau, 1976-1999 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Everwine, Peter, 2002-2005 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Faerstein, Howie, 2004-2007 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Fairchild, Peter, 2000-2002 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Farnsworth, Robert, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Farragher, Shaun, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Fishman, Charles, 1986-1993 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Flynn, Nick, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - Flynn, Tom, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - Fraser, Kathleen, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - Friebert, Stuart, 1987-1995 (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Fried, Daisy, 2005 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Fox, Robert and Foster, Jeanne, 1987-2004 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Frost, Carol, 1998-2004 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Galvin, James (Box 20, Folder 87)
    - Garber, Fred, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 88)
    - Garcia, Richard, 2004 (Box 20, Folder 89)